A Guide to the Office of the Vice President for Administration, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1977-1984
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Office of the Vice President for Administration, University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1977-1984
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/1/2.861
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1986 July 24.
Contents List
- SERIES I: General Files
  - Action Teams 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Action Teams--Evaluation of Action Team Process 1983 (Box 1)
  - V-P for Administration--Planning Process for Units (meeting Campbell,Kovatch) 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - V-P for Administration--Year-End Results, 1982-1983 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - Staff Meeting (4 folders) 1982 Sep-Dec (Box 1)
  - Staff Meeting (6 folders) 1983 Jan-Jun (Box 1)
  - Visitors--Meeting 1982 Jun 4-7 (Box 1)
  - Visitors--Meeting 1982 Oct 14-16 (Box 1)
  - Visitors--Meeting 1983 Jan 20-22 (Box 1)
  - Visitors--Meeting 1983 Mar 24-26 (Box 1)
  - Visitors--Meeting 1983 Jun 2-4 (Box 2)
  - Visitors--Finance Committee 1983 (Box 2)
  - ADCOM: Six-Year Administrative Computing Plan (Request for Proposal) 1982 (Box 2)
  - ADCOM: "Proposal for a Six-Year Administrative Computing Plan, Arthur Anderson and Company 1982 (Box 2)
  - ADCOM: Oral Presentation, Arthur Anderson and Co. 1982 May 28 (Box 2)
  - ADCOM: "ADCOM Review Report" 1982 Aug 12 (Box 2)
  - ADCOM: "Six-Year Administrative Computing Plan" 1982 Nov (Box 2)
  - Budget Office (2 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 2)
  - Budget Office--1983-1984 Budget Reviews 1983-1984 (Box 2)
  - Budget Office--1986-1990 Capital Budget (for 1984-1986 Capital Budget, see "Budget Briefings in Richmond") 1983 (Box 2)
  - Budget Briefings in Richmond 1983 Jan-Mar (Box 2)
  - Budget Cuts (2 folders) 1982 -1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget Process--Addenda 1983 Jul (Box 3)
  - Budget--Computing and Communications 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Equal Employment Opportunity 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Fringe Benefits 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--General Services 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Materiel Management 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Personnel Office 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Physical Plant 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Police 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Police 911 Emergency Response 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Printing and Mail 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Real Estate/Budget, Risk Management 1983-1984 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Commerce School--Planning 1977-1983 (Box 3)
  - Budget--Computing and Communications 1982-1983 (Box 3)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs 1982 (Box 4)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs (Affirmative Action) 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs 1983 (Box 4)
  - Faulkner House 1984 (Box 4)
  - Materiel Management (3 folders) 1982-1983 (Box 4)
  - Materiel Management--Transfer of Storeroom from Hospital 1982 Sep-Dec (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - Parents' Day Weekend 1982 (Box 5)
  - Personnel Office 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - Physical Plant 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - Police Department 1982-1983 (Box 5)
  - Policies and Procedures 1983 (Box 5)
  - President's Office 1981-1983 (Box 5)
  - President's Office--Senate and House Bills, Sandy Gilliam 1983 (Box 5)
  - Printing Office 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Real Estate (2 folders) 1979-1983 (Box 6)
  - Real Estate-Del Greco Easement 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Real Estate--Overlook 1981-1983 (Box 6)
  - Real Estate--"Woodlawn" Currie Estate 1982 (Box 6)
  - Risk Management 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Risk Management--Safety Director 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Risk Management--Insurance Claims 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Risk Management--UVa. Insurance Policies 1983 (Box 6)
  - Risk Management--Workmen's Compensation, Sub-committee Studying Self-Insurance for 1982 Feb-Jun (Box 6)
  - Sprigg Lane--Client-Lawyer Relationship 1982-1983 (Box 6)
  - Vice-Presidential Planning Group--past 1981-1982 (Box 7)
  - Vice-Presidential Planning Group 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Vice-Presidential Planning Group (2 folders) 1983-1984 (Box 7)
- SERIES II: Committee Files
  - Administrative Committees 1983 (Box 7)
  - Arboretum Committee 1983 (Box 7)
  - Architectural Advisory Committee 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Asbestos Projects 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Assistant Vice-President for Administrative Computing [Search Committee] 1983-1984 (Box 7)
  - Building Committee--Faulkner Residence Halls 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - Building Committee--Gilmer Hall Addition 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Handicapped Access, Phase III 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--INMD/Cardiology Research Lab 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Medical Center Parking Garage 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Newcomb Hall Addition, Phase III 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Montebello Residence Renovation 1983 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Nuclear Magnetic Resonance Unit Renovation 1983 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Replacement Hospital 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Replacement Hospital: Program and Planning Committee 1982 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Replacement Hospital: Executive Committee 1983 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Replacement Hospital: Renovation of Bldg. 203, Engineering (old Printing Building) 1984 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Sprigg Lane Housing Design-Build Project 1982-1983 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Sponsor's Hall 1982 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Student Activity Building 1982 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--Utilities 1982 (Box 8)
  - Building Committee--1105 W. Main (Old Sears Building) 1983-1984 (Box 8)
  - Cemetery 1983 (Box 9)
  - Chapel Committee 1983 (Box 9)
  - Cost Saving Committee 1983 (Box 9)
  - Energy Conservation Committee 1983 (Box 9)
  - School of Education--Dean's Search Committee 1984 (Box 9)
  - Graphics Committee 1983 (Box 9)
  - Landscape Steering Committee 1984 (Box 9)
  - Master Plan Committee (3 folders) 1982-1984 (Box 9)
  - Medical Center Space and Cost Allocation Committee 1983-1984 (Box 9)
  - Residential Life Committee 1982 (Box 9)
  - Service Awards Committee 1984 (Box 9)
  - Special Materials Handling Facility Committee 1982 (Box 9)
  - Special Projects Committee--$35,000 1983 (Box 9)
  - Special Projects Committee--$10,000 Allotment 1983 (Box 9)
  - Systems Planning Committee 1983-1984 (Box 9)
  - University-Industrial Technology Committee 1984 (Box 9)